question_data = [
    {
        "response_code": 0,
        "results": [
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "DragonForce's 'Through the Fire and Flames' is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "\"Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater\" takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Tony Hawk's Pro Skater was released in 1999.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "TF2: The Heavy's voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "In \"Call Of Duty: World At War\", the first appearance of the \"PPSH-41\" in \"Zombies\" was in the map \"Der Riese\".",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in \"Forza Horizon 3\".",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "In the Season One Championship of \"League of Legends\", the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
]
